新人类（下）（2010年星际政治峰会）
翻译：柯维
(中文字幕 英文是翻译参考)
好的 让我再给你们展示另一个小的案例 我在全世界范围内遇见了那些遭遇了外星访客的人 他们说出了这类语言
right let's just give you another little example all around the world i meet people that come out with these languages that had encounters
很是令我着迷 因为我想理解更多的内容
and its been fascinating for me because i've wanted to understand more
再次的这很像是连线拼图
and again it's like doing the dots
Donna Redfield写作了五本书 其中的两本是关于外星访客的 令人伤心的是她已经过世了
donna redfield is an author of five books two of them are battering countess at least is not with us anymore
但她曾在美国居住的时候和我有过一段时间的联系
but dont know i communicated with a number of times she lived in america
她的两本书《萨满》和《人族外星人》(The ET-human link)都与她的经历有关
took her books some under and the human eighty link without her experiences
我给她送去了崔西讲话的DVD
and i sent half a dvd tracy speaking
之后她对我说“当崔西说起悦耳的外星语言时 我开始随着崔西说了起来 就好像是我在参与一场双向的对话”
and she said to me when tracy began to speak in the musical language i spoke along with her almost
对她来说真的是难以置信
at the pi were engaging in a two-way conversation which was in quant quite incredible to her
我遇见过许多来找过我的人 他们中有些人听到了这些语言之后会说 他们也做过同样的事情 不过他们从没有说起过
i have had to many people come to me that if that some of the languages and say
我收集了大量的这类绘画及图片文件 他们都是在无意识间下载的
many different and drawings not wo and i've got a great deal more things in fact files of it with a download it without any conscious thought and it seems not in trons
但他们与此相连接的时候都有一种美妙的感觉
but they have an amazing feeling of connection to it
让我们再看看崔西对此是怎么说的
so let's see what tracie egan says about this
该语言更加准确的代表了某个个体灵魂的震动   那意味着该语言直接来自宇宙意识或神的本质 基本上将一切存有都连接在了一起
the language is a more accurate representation of an individual soul vibration .it means ut the language comes directly from the essence of the universal mind or call it hich alice mailings all the existence together
某种特定语言的声音趋向于意识的线性逻辑等方面
the spoken sounds of a particular language tend to bypass much of the linear logical aspects of consciousness
因此没有来自意识的思维输入
therefore there is  no input from the conscious mind
这种语言没有结构 因此与那部分没有任何关系
the language has no structure and is therefore not related to the part in any way
所以在它通过线性的时空之前那是它最纯粹的形式
that whole in its purest form before it becomes vocal it by pass union spacetime
很有趣 不是吗
which is quite interesting isn't it
语言是一个灵魂直接与另一个灵魂无意识状态连接的产物 没有架构可以解释声音的振动的即时性 而且无法准确的用英语解释或其他任何语言在这里说明
the language is the creation of the soul in a way that directly connects with the soul of another unconsciously .there is no framework as the interpretation of the sound vibration is instantaneous and cannot be accurately interpret it into english or any other language spoken at this time
它还教导了我们的灵魂和他人的灵魂沟通
it's teaching us to communicate with also linden soles about this this is one
这是从用词语表达沟通到心灵沟通的一步
of the steps from where it's to telepathic communication
语言本身会阻碍信息完全自由的流动 因为将信息翻译成我们的发音需要一段时间
these languages blocks of information translating fatter quite some time
通常你需要
off and that you would need to fill the whole house looking factor p_t_a_s
将这些信息翻译成我们的发音可能用上几秒钟的时间
and in actually turns exits that may be related to in a few seconds
有些可能与我们相近的振动是这样的
the sample greetings classified facial he'll need not to send them out
这句话的意思是 我们已经到达了进化的某个阶段 机会已经不是我们想象的那样了 一切都已就绪
piecemeal be reaching stationary position is no longer have to imagine
我们开始将拼图游戏的碎片拼凑在了一起 而且意识到我们在宇宙中的角色
and women-owned during the conflict critics of the food together
"我们在宇宙中的角色" 她是这么说的
our part in the universe is what she's saying
米雪儿这位女士所谈的
so what we shall is talking about that
不止是她自己具有星际孩童意识的事实
is not only the fact that she is aware of heroin and stark child to a consciousness
而且她还意识到许多语言    在某种意义上来说
but she is aware of what many of the languages uh... about in the sense that
不是所有的这些语言都可以被我们以常规的方式翻译过来   比如以圣诞节的概念为例
not all of them come we translate in normal ways it's it's like using the concept of the work christmas for example
圣诞节立即带来了大量的信息 从圣诞树到你做的晚餐 到装礼物的包裹 一切的一切
amazing things in all this other information from christmas trees to you know what you cook for dinner to the parcels and everything
而圣诞节只是一个词 这点有些类似 不过更加复杂而已
but it's just one word and it's similar to that only a lot more complex
这些符号和手稿是古代的信息沟通形式 无须逐页阅读
the symbols and script are the ancient forms of communicating volumes of information without having to read pages and pages
我把这些叫做压缩文件 而且我认为此刻很多人下载了这些信息都有很重要的原因
and these compressed files and i think that's a very important reason why they're being downloaded at the moment into many of these individuals
因此我相信 有可能是因为我们正被协助着由语言沟通到心灵沟通进化
so what i'd believe at the possibility is that we're being assisted to go from federal communication to collect the faith
某种方式上解释了那一点的原因是Chrisl谈到的
and one of the ways of explaining that is what chris i'll talks about
她说：
she says this
比如在飞行教学的课程中
for example in lectures when the lectures in for flight teaching
他的或她的思想完全的向学生敞开 我发现我可以进入到他们的脑海中直接吸收概念
and his or her mind is completely open to students i found i could just go into their mind and it's all of the concepts directly
我不必不要靠听他们的讲话而学习了
i'm not primarily listening to their words
而是在他们的脑海中自己提取概念
but in their minds with them extracting the concepts myself
这样省去了很多误解
this second that's a lot of misunderstanding
我感觉这些孩子们也做了同样的事情
i feel these refined children are doing the same
我教导到 我会在讲话的同时确保我的思维也是完全开放的
i have taught have made so my mind is completely open while speaking
正在进行的是一场思想的移植 我的知识库正同他们的融合在了一起
there was thought transplanting going on my bank of information was merged with the
他们会重新将知识系统化
and they re-schematized their own knowledge systems accordingly
当然符号会是这个书写管道  就像是非语言的社会
of course singles would be the written conduit for this like a normal experts
传授神秘知识时需要面对面的老师教导
society save eighteen grease with the mystical knowledge could only be passed on face to face by mid deck teacher
但是这些古代的符号承载了概念上的关键点 可以触发内在的观察思维 而非像我们今天这样的教学
but agent symbols hold the conceptual keys the trigger within the observing minds with our teaching a being present
在这些人和孩子们身上发生的经历
what is happening with people kids who have these experiences is more a
不同于我们历代祖辈们通过线性逐页的阅读学习
different way of learning to not generally accepted linear a way of learning reading pages and pages
这是我们的符号触发的扩展 崔西提到
this is an extension of our symbol trigger mention by tracy
随你怎么想
so make about what you will
可以告诉我们你在写什么吗
commuters who you're going to be three-ring
当然 这真的很像是将古代文明遗失的信息翻译出来
translating information that the snow and by featured civilizations groups of giving
关于这些文字我无法给你一个更准确的描述
them more accurate description of peace
我的星球更矮小一些
must on expedia children his require that may be indicates
但是在每个字符之内 再次的就像是那些语言一样 它本身就是块信息
they didn't make the languages it's really like a broken informatio
如果你能以三维的角度描述每个字符 因为我是那样看每个字符的 那就更加准确了
if you were able to get three-dimensional ,depiction of each caracter  because that's how i feel each one that would be much more accurate
这些信息通过我传达出来 因为我意识到自己多维度的属性
p_o_w_'s mentioned incomes ni i'm aware of it being multifaceted
当我做疗愈工作的时候 我在空气中和能量场中看到一些编码
dealing with rings c coding in the air and in the energy proves and seasoning in anywhere
我把这些编码看作是数字 就如同你们看数学构图
members like human mathematical configuration
或者我把它们看作是电码点 或者是端口 你可以用很多不同的方式看待它们
well i'm lazy and or can actually see them as political there many different ways that you can view them
或者你可以把他们看作是声音 和这些文字是一样的
or you can steven i've found the same with the writing
你在做这件事的时候感觉怎么样 你有什么样的感觉
and we'd be megan and that you're doing
我感到非常快乐
very happy million
当我以这种方式表达的时候 当我以这种人们叫做外星语言或者是外星文字表达的时候
icing in these ways when an expressing migrating languages
对我来说非常非常的自然 相比较于人类形式的表达
eighty writing if he is much more natural for me than the human forms of expression
我猜这些都与我的外星意识有关
cities has to do with my gym consciously
事实上对我而言 学着做一个人类要比学做外星人……
it is really learning about things
你们听到最后一部分了吗   “学着做一个人类要比学着做个外星人更难”  她实际上不得不学习做一个人类
make you and hit the lost about it's more about learning to be human and being an eggs and then being extraterrestrial she's actually having to learn to be human and
她是那么说的 我有件没有提到的事情是
that's what she's talking about and one of the things that i haven't included here
我还询问了她是怎么阅读这些手稿的 她说她把手放在上方
is i also how she this kind of script and she was describing that she puts a hand over the top of it
就像扫描一样
and waited like a kind of paul kind warehouse
和那个五岁的小男孩做的完全是同样的事情
on what does that five year old little boy did exactly the same thing
再次的 我发现有很多很多人 如北美的Doona 他们画出了一系列令人着迷的复杂图画
again what i found with others like donna in north america and many many others they do and a range of interesting a fascinating complex torrance
这是Donna画的 我不会进一步解释了 因为我在第一次介绍中已经提到过了
this summer donna's i won't go into the explanation here because they're actually on my first presentation
我只想给你们一些关于这些复杂的作品的一些概念 很明显的显示出了这些人身上正在发生着一些事情
and so i'm just where you want to give you some idea of the complexity of some of the artwork which certainly showing something's going on with these individuals
专业的说是他们正在同他们的外星访客们之间发生了一些事情
intense of what experiences that happening in and their encounters
当然还有这些奇怪的手稿
anand course coming out with the same strange scripts
我见过太多这类手稿了 我有来自世界各地的人们的提供这类文件
i see so much of a citizen uni rates it's sort of um... i've got files of the from people from all of the world
有些非常类似 而有些又非常不同
that some of it is very similar some of it is quite different
这是Donna画的 她对此有着惊人的理解
this is some of donna's and she has done a fascinating understanding off them as well
这也是她的作品
this is more of her work
这是一幅崔西画的画 你可以看出非常的繁杂
and this is one of tracy's as you can see is is very busy
也同样令人着迷
but it's also quite fascinating
可以看到在每个画点之中似乎携带了大量的信息 这正是我谈过的压缩文件
to see that each tiny bit of it seems to hold the corrected information and this is where i'm talking about the complex files
崔西还画了黑白画
that tracy authentic black and white ones
在你们右侧看到的是 你会看到这幅奇怪的图像
and actually to the right if you think you'll see this strange uh... image
这幅画大概是崔西在去埃及的六七年前画的
this is something that tracy did probably about six to seven years before she went to egypt
她说这幅特别的画对她来说意义非凡
and she said that this particular one was particularly fascinating to her
我解释一下她是怎么说的
and then let me just explain what she said about it
她说这是￥%#@……！
she said that this was a car not conducting up luxor and she knew
她立即了解到她适合这幅画
immediately she took the same age we've had that it would fit
她谈到金字塔不止是意识和能量的放大器及聚焦源
and she was not a talking about the pyramids pink lunches energetic an amplifiers and focusing power source
她还说：我知道这个适用于远程作用
she also said i knew that this would fit from a distance
我之所以知道是因为我有种强烈的感觉要带上它
i knew it and fit because i have a strong feeling to take it with me
然后她说道她之所以画出那幅特别的图画是这样的
and then she said the reason that she had draw on that particular image was this
荷鲁斯来到了我的梦中
whole earth came to me in a dream
我身处于地下墓穴或是洞穴之中
i wasn't in underground carven or cave
他给我在墙上展示了一些埃及的符号
he was showing me some addiction higher interest on the wall
这些都雕刻墙上了
this almost carved into the war with his next time
然后他们逐渐变大 我又在地面上看到了这些符号 背景是拂晓时的小山
and then he grow in size and i was above the ground looking at the symbol with hills in sunrise in the background
这是来自远古时代的神圣符号 帮助我们觉醒并唤起我们到底是谁
it's a sacred symbol from ancient times to help us awaken and remember who we are
我发现非常有趣 这些还是她的画
which i found quite fascinating these are some more of her drawings
这是关于她是如何理解金字塔以及其他的古代神圣之地
and how she understands anton and beat the pyramids and other ancient sacred sites
我会给你们展示似乎正在发生的一些事情
so i'm not going to show you what seems to happen very much
嗨 我叫米歇尔 杜利亚
prime minister said to him
我有八年的时间清楚的知道我和外星人有过接触 而且我整个一生都有这类接触
have been consciously aware of
我与外星人的这些经历非常奇特 我经历了一个过程
my expenses greenbacks restrooms having plan hearings i have gone through pricing
现在八年过去了 我遇到了许多戏剧化的事情
mountain anaconda dramatic aspect
我的这一经历带给了我很多启示 尤其是我的疗愈能力
and now that my expenses particularly in the way in hell healing abilities
对我治疗工作有很大的帮助
i myself expansion of muslim plan hearing work
我可以说许多外星语言
chinese speaking and many people
我还可以书写外星文字
detail and put his and i'll send runs canadian scrapers
这些能力对我来说都很自然
sit abilities or comp time explaining to me
你是怎么意识到你可以治疗的？你又是怎么理解你的这种治疗工作？
how do you wear if the fact that you could heal what is your understanding and thinking that you can beginning work return
我做的这些治疗工作多年来一直在改变和进步
sandoval continuously first began
我第一次这样的经历是有天凌晨3点我被带出了我的房子 我看着月亮
it first began when i had an experience i was draw out of my house about 3 am and i was looking at the moon
当我看着月亮时 我感觉非常奇怪 我觉得月亮和我的距离太近了
and so when i was looking at the moon ,i feel quit strange ,i feel too close to my eyes
而我闭上双眼时 各种不同的感觉涌上心头
when i close my eyes ,i feel a lot of  different sensations
我眼前出现了无数的爆破
phillips her collecting them around us entertainment
我的手指上和脸上都有不同的感觉
i had in picking through all that much i had some the sensation of queens said coming with my head and i could feel it
我可以感觉到鼻子上的骚动
could be my notes
耳朵里出现了不同的声音
they also have sound waves that were going into my ear
而这一现象不断的出现
from the greatest ski resort here too as an entire
我的头脑中也出现了奇妙的想法
huang tingling sensation zone and i had a smile
这一过程持续了一段时间
this crisis a month sometime
当它停下来之后 我发现我又睁开了双眼
and when it's done i can't recognize the king
我感觉我的身体非常的沉重
heavy maja dancing
身体里还有另一个人
it's in my pocket
我只好走进自己的内在 平躺在床上
understand joins coincides live down in my bed
当我躺下之后我开始在自己身上搜寻些什么东西
and when i let them and there is an excuse to
我以前从没有做过这种事
cancer research and i think i'm independent
我从没有对自己或者是他人做过疗愈的工作
going ahead and exp parents there
然后 我在我的身上移动我的双手
so uh... i had my hangs in making
手指尖开始一种新的运动方式
the healing involed my new movement my finger tips
我运用我的手指 啪啪快速晃动
old money movement since nineteen eighty thing my fingers they felt as though they were playing wii imagines pickup exchange
那就是我的感觉
disconnect there
我会做一系列的连续动作
irewards a series of consecutive movement
我会察觉到疗愈工作是否起作用了
and occurred googlecareer actor and penetrating three-mile grins
我会把我的手指锁定在某个姿势和位置上
i would have been my fingers uh... syndrome
然后我会运用一些非常特别的动作
lost in a position planks a  and then i would choose series and
我用我的肌肉和眼睛解开或者释放掉那些压力
their specific movements muscles in my richard tan and walk six percent
实际上会将我的身体摆出不同的姿势
i had to actually make my body in two different positions to access called nine one season five
随着年复一年的时间流逝 我的疗愈工作也随之而改变 我会运用我的整只手而不只是手指
very healing work that i was doing extremely
我并没有有意识的使用我的眼睛
as much time to sing
不久之后我开始使用音调进行工作
then later on i started time now is in insulated believed i had to use the time
后来出现了语言
and then later language
出现了语言之后 我就开始将语言和音调结合起来使用于治疗当中
after the languages entertainment i started using a combination of china and members
之后又出现了歌声 我可以解释为这些歌声可以让灵魂认可
have been mistaken very pleased with the cells to recognize
灵魂可以回忆起这些歌声来自其他星球 来自前世
souls maryland manner of the line
这些歌声帮助那些人感到舒适 以便进行一些特殊的疗愈工作
really they used
真的有时就像是人类哼着“啦啦吧”哄着婴儿睡觉 这些歌声可以帮他们放松
as you might lose
这些歌声可以转换思维 帮助一些人进入另一种状态
medicards
（以下为外星歌曲的吟唱 @#%！%~￥~~~）
米歇尔谈到的是她的疗愈能力
what's and myself doing that is actually stopping about healing
事实上是在她发现与月亮的特殊经历之后
and about the fact that she found often experience with the moon
月球在这里是非常重要的 因为许多人谈到月亮很圆很大  而我猜想那根本不是月球
and the mood is very important here because a lot of people talk about the moon being around all and a very big men my suspicion is it's not
实际上是某个宇宙飞船
when they're all that it's actually one of the card
但是她谈到她被带到月亮上面的经历
but she talks about having experience which she was going outside
在她的耳朵里响起的那些奇怪的声音
and felt the strange sounds going into her heheh hearing
当她进入内在时 她开始做一些奇怪的动作   她把这些叫做自我心理手术
and when she went inside she started to do strange movements which she called psyche surgery on herself
那之后她开始进行了疗愈的工作 她运用音调
after that she was going to healing and she uses toning
她运用不同的声音 令人着迷的是
she uses different sounds and what's fascinating about it is
她真的对她的行为有着复杂的理解
that she has a really complex understanding of what she's doing
我致力于重新调整.....就像是我在使用音叉一样 就像是你们在演奏一件乐器
i worked to re-tune .......like i use a tuning fork,like you would a musical instrument
我把当时某个人最需要的频率带过来
i do this by bringing in the frequencies the person most needs at the time
既使用声音 又使用彩色符号 就如我们的多维度本质一样
both sounds and colored symbols ,as we are malted immensely nation out
你们有些人可能会对此感到困惑
so this is going to haps confront some of your
我还是想给你们看看
but i want to just a very nice
当我做疗愈工作的时候 我会将自己由人类自我转换成外星人自我 听起来也许会有点奇怪
workers in here power no male brain it's like unicef excuse my eighty-seven device and a big strands back
我会处理一些进入到我的意识中的信息
have been given information that about money into a consciousness
我可以更好的在外星人人格和人类人格中平衡和转换
i can better this consiousness coming into this  coming into this thing heading accolades eighteen lines human characteristics
我的人类自我非常的敏感 非常的情绪化
martinez dot there is anything to an area national my excuse them
我的外星自我非常理性 非常实际
used very clinical very impractical nanny matter-of-fact
我在做治疗工作的时候 我会让外星自我主导
beginning with the right to and printing saying
很像是一个外科医生在工作
it is really like a readiness surgeon
我非常清楚的看到能量场 被治疗者的问题所在
why see very clearly and energy fields the problem and anemic
我会修复好它 不会牵扯进我个人的情感
fix-it there's no agreement for our international involvement my personality
我可以听见哪里的能量出现了不和谐的音调
when aspects the signs and hyatt he had a lot of energy field is out of cheating
不是以我们常规的方式聆听
i drank a demand the way you normally here
我以另一种方式倾听 通常我们是听不到的
among other things if you're not really going on in the eighties
我会听到某些部位的能量出现不和谐的音调
set in place in mt theo salute the answer cheating
然后我会重新调整音调 就像是你用音叉给乐器重新定音一样
and spyware to reaching almost like you to sixteen to human musical instruments
我是这样做的
halides he's is
我会把某个人在当时最需要的频率带给他
by bringing in the frequency purpose and nicely onto the streets and angkana
我通过声音和颜色带给他
ends wide open symbols come craig
通常我也会将这些声音翻译成符号 这些符号本身都是多维度的
stands expands the as well dissonance and all of the things minister
它们不像是我们通常使用的普通的形状
within normal life normal shapes
我会同一个团队合作 大约有六到十个不同的生命会协助我
their release work with the team usually of about six to ten different beings to help me
我的团队会因为我的需要而改变
as nineteen exp changes and society
通常我不喜欢给同我一起工作的生命起名字或者给他们做标记
each day i turn like to named the things that are working all identified and i think
对我来说 意识到能量比其他事情都重要
for me it's just important that i'm aware of payment in more than anything else
但是他们会给我一个名字 以便我感觉舒服 而且会更好的熟悉他们
they will give meaning nd helps them to feel comfortable and will continue with and the client
我的客户在治疗会话之后通常会感到放松 更加的平衡
usually rule feel relaxed and physician using things 1few more balance
很多次 他们的灵魂会离开他们的身体 我意识到他们在会话期间离开了身体
quite often they won't believe they employ you i will look like is the
他们可能意识到的是他们睡着了 但实际上不是这样的
winner of a third party during the session they may be in the everglades
他们在会话期间离开身体一段时间 治疗会话大概一个半小时
isolated um... but it's actually quite different and the israelis at acceptance
这是非常深层次的工作 有意识的思维不会参与其中
and tolerance instances we haha incidences this is so people were can take place without him and being involved
你们中有些人会对此有疑惑
for some of you on pre-civil font
我发现这点真的很有趣 因为我同许多做能量疗愈的人谈过 他们都接触过外星访客
so i thought it was really interesting 'cause i've talked to many people text do energy work that had encounters
崔西说她十五岁的时候意识到她手上的能量
what rolls and into in tracy talked about being aware of any tina hands which was fifteen
我想要了解的更多
so i want to understand more
不止是他们使用的语言 还有他们对此事理解的深度 我会对此进一步的多谈谈
that not a the language in the the depth of their understanding office i'm going to go into that in a minute
我以科学的角度对此进行观察 因为我有看护助产科的背景
i've been looking at science it because my backgrounds nursing midwifery
我还需要用三维的术语来进行量化 这样对我来说才有意义
i still need to quantify that infinite dimensional terms that make sense to me
我发现了一些真正有趣的事情
and i found something really very interesting
这是一份近来俄罗斯的研究报告 已经翻译成了德语
and this is to do with them recent russian research which was actually translated into german
这是弗朗斯 鲁道夫的作品
this is the work upon gracie authors on france laid off
他提出我们的DNA可以由语言和频率影响而重新编写
and he suggests guardian a can be influenced in reprogram by words in frequencies
无须切断或替换某个基因
without cutting out all replacing single genes
基因学家和语言学家都发现 DNA不仅对我们的身体结构起反映
and the geneticists and linguists have found that d_n_a_ is not only responsible for the construction of all parties
而且还是一个存储库
but says it's a dot a storage
可以同语言进行某种程度上的沟通 它仅仅需要的是适当的频率
and in communication follows the same roles as language it just requires the right frequencies
我们这里听到的是
now what we're hearing here
某种程度上某些语言实际上可以改变DNA
that somehow or other some language actually can alter denying
有很多外星接触者告诉我
now one of these uh... so a lot of these individuals having me
他们使用语言、音调、声音来进行治疗
that today use language towns they using sound
对我而言 更重要的是其他一些事情
to me what's the difference the something else with that
他们还说到：
what they also said laws
DNA的本质就像全息的计算机 信息可以由震动和频率传送
that the nature of dna alike holographic computers information can be transmitted by vibration and frequency
他们称做基因波
wave geneticsthey call weight genetics
他们还发现：DNA在真空中会引起扰乱 产生磁性的虫洞
they've also found dna conchords disturbing patents in a vacuum producing magnetized when halls
这些渠道连接了宇宙的不同区域
he's a tunnel connections between entirely different areas of the universe
信息会经过空间和时间而传播开来
to reach information is transmitted through space and time
DNA吸引信息 它构成了我们意识的一部分 在一种完全放松的状态下形成超意识沟通
dna extract this information it part isn't well consciousness high-power communication in the state of relax ation
现在听听米歇尔说了什么 以及她是如何理解她所做的事情
now listen to what we shall facts his hair and a standing of what she's doing
和我一起工作的那些生命们想要指出 身体的不同部分是怎么相互作用的
they're being so we're working with me we're wanting to areas in the party actually interact
所以我的手放在身体的不同部位 用手指向身体的不同位置
seminar space in their hands across pointing out different sections of the budget
这是展示给包括你在内的观众看的 身体的每个部分都不是彼此独立的
this is for the audiens as well as for you  it was just showing how each part of the body is not independent
在其它领域里身体的各部分协同工作
off any other  area they all work together
而我们认识到身体作为一个整体运作是十分重要的
and it is important we recognise this we see the body as a whole
手臂 经过特殊的触碰 给身体的每个部分以一定的频率
arm their today  time for civilian and returns and according to an end to admiration
通过特殊的触碰,实际上就激活了某个区域
man named martin expressing returned to normal been envy bank and inaction activity began airing man
他们同样也连接了来自不同的星球和纬度的能量
they also have an incident in includes environment intend to
如果你喜欢的话 我们可以这样来想象：我们的身体就是宇宙
uh... sophia loren where mentioned that the body is the universe
我们太阳系的所有行星都在它之内
and and it's been our solar system monitors exist thinking
我们使它们在一起协同运作
so remaking the working together
在每一个脉轮中都有所有的行星
and meeting each show balikpapan sexist  and within each chakra
所以我们现在所做的 就是为这个特别的容器（身体）激活某个适当的行星
and so we're just activating the appropriate cannons particular vessel at this time
下一次也许激活其他的行星 不过它们都存在于每个脉轮当中
others will be activated on the town's video existed
而每个脉轮都具有多维度本质
anti semitism wilson won't fit simpson mentioned
并非如我们想象的只是七个脉轮
it is now has been indicted
每个脉轮都有很多层面的
fitness standards many testing
我发现非常有趣的是 如今我们对DNA有了更进一步的理解
are not really interesting when we're looking at what we know about d_n_a_ now
至少是这些研究者对DNA所作的说明
and or at least what these researchers are indicating delay
现在 让我们再进一步的研究下去
let's take this one step not and third
自从我作护士的时候就对一个问题很感兴趣
i've been really interested from mine nis midwife days online
为什么我们有这个DNA之谜？  不止是因为我们的DNA中有223对基因组意外的出现在我们的进化过程中
why we have this d_n_a_ mystery of us not only we have two hundred twenty-three genomes inot denying it is a sideways in session of genetic material that did not come up through the investment phase of our revolution
那部分基因组同样也包含了更高级的心理机能所需的一切   它们到底来自何处
that is also part of uh... uh... which actually contains everything to do with higher psychological functioning  where did they  come from
那本身正是许多人探索的谜题
that in itself is a mystery that many people are exploring
还有一些令我感兴趣的是 最近的一些研究 专业术语上来说是DNA之谜 所谓的“垃圾DNA”
but what i was also interested in is some of the latest research in in terms of a d_n_a_ mystery intense about junk d_n_a_
据说是 首先我们只使用了我们大脑的五分之一
what is being said is that first of all we only use one fifth of our brain
为什么会是那样
why is that
我们的基因组中有三十亿对碱基对 而只有六千万对是激活的
we have three billion base pairs genomes in the genetic code returnees sixty million are active
为什么
why?
这些碱基对携带的信息从未解读过 我们只靠着我们DNA的百分之三就生存下来了
this information they carries never read we only exist on three percent on our DNA ?
一些致力于人类基因组项目研究人员有了惊人的发现
a group of researchers   working on the human genome project maintenance tarnishing discovery
他们相信所谓的未解码的序列 也就是人类DNA中的97% 与未知的外星生命形式有着千丝万缕的联系
they believe the so-called noncoding sequences which is ninety seven percent in human d_n_a_ on no less than that genetic code of unknown extraterrestrial life form
研究小组负责人Tribe教授所说的：
this is professor tribe the group leader
我们所见的DNA是一套包含了两个版本的编码程序:“ 大编码版”和“基本编码版”
what we see our d_n_a_ is a program consisting of two versions: be cord and the basic cord
他相信完整的编码一定不只在地球上存在
the complete program was positively not only on earth he police
他说 基因本身不足以解释进化
he says the genes by themselves are not enough to explain evolution
就好比微软要升级就离不开BASIC语言
no creates a beate programa from mars microsoft would not leave the program without an option for improvement or upgrade
升级包已经存在于所谓的垃圾DNA中
no create be the upgrade is already closed in the junk d_n_a_
他建议说: 这只不过是隐藏在我们的基本编码之中
i he says jesse not it is nothing more than a hidden domain upgrade of our  basic code
我们已经知道某些特别的宇宙射线有能量可以修改DNA
we already know that certain kosmicrays have the power to modify d_n_a_
因此,这看来是可以接受的
so it is plausible he says
外星的编码只要从宇宙的某处射出一道适当的能量
that the extraterrestrial program has made us she is one slash at the right energy from somewhere in the universe
就可以给基本编码以指令 移去它的阻碍 自我溶解为“大编码版”
to instruct the basic code to remove its blocks and reef and fuse itself to the big cut
而那一旦发生 将会永远的改变我们
that with changes for ever
我们中有些人会在数月内
some of us within months
将不会再有癌症 疾病或者短暂的生命了
it being a more palaces diseases and a short line
在智力上我们会有如弹弓弹射般的飞跃
i would catapult us intellectually
就好比是大哥大手机和智能手机之间的区别
the comparison would be the difference between the you know and the full and the chrome acronyms
这整个规划非常巧妙 而且是自我组织的
this complete program is elegant self organizing
就像是给一台非常高级的生物电脑软件校正
auto correcting software for a highly advanced biological computer
一个是有疾病的短暂的生命 另一个是有潜在的超级智能的、健康长寿的超人
the difference between a short disease life and potential for a super intelligent seetha being with a long and healthy life
那么那些“下载”呢 那些外星的文字和图画 语言 以及麦田圈都是这场能量升级的一部分吗
so what about the downloads the scripts the language the crop circles is is part of the energetic upgrade
与我们的DNA都有关系吗
and be on c_n_n_
要记得我们在此谈论的是一次恰当的能量闪爆
remember we're talking about a flash of the right energy
这些都是这次升级的一部分吗？这些都是唤醒我们的一部分吗？是帮助我们醒来的吗？
so what are these as part of that upgrade all these positive us waking up aunty helping us to wake up
这些古代的符号真的也是协助这一进化过程的吗
on the three ancient symbols that are actually assisting this process of evolution
非常确定的是 许多人已经受到了它们的影响
certainly many people affected by them
不仅是因为他们（麦田圈）看上去美轮美奂 更是因为当我们置身其中的时候感受到各种非常强大的频率
not just because they're amazing to look at but when our insight and feel all sorts of very powerful frequencies
包括疗愈能量
including healing
Freddie Celebra 在他的书《Secrets in the field》中含蓄的指出：麦田圈是宇宙语言 我们不断的听到有人这么说
and freddie celebrating his book secrets in the field suggests that critic by implication be that the crop circles are on a universal language we keep hearing that word
他们还做了些什么呢
but what else are they doing
稍等片刻
on on commands dot that just a second
我们这里看到的是潜在的可能
so we're looking at the potential here
在某种程度上 那些“压缩文件”或是“下载”
that's in some way possibly as compressed files or downloads
我很好奇 我非常好奇
i wonder and i know anyone drain
那些“压缩文件”是否就是给“新电脑”准备的“新软件”
whether in fact i was compressed files in fact all the new software for the new computer
Chen教授说：届时我们最终一旦“启动”,我们就需要一套新的操作软件
that when we finally get switched on if thats what what professor china's talking about we going to need a new operating software
我不知道 这些“下载”和“压缩文件”是不是为了这些新电脑准备的新软件
i wonder if in fact these downloads of compressed files and the new software for the new computer
我真的不知道
i really don't know
但这是个很有趣的想法
the distancing thought
在我进一步深入下去之前
now just before i go in the fact that
我会给你们一个简单的回顾 我们做的不错 还会有时间进行一些问答互动
i'd just want to give you an overview of this crash eating very well for time so i might even be out on some questions
苏珊 汉森是我的一位非常特殊的客户 她一生都与外星经历有关
says that hanson as uh... very dear friend of mine has had experience is all her life
她从前是一位老师
cheese that form a teacher
她现如今住在新西兰
she now runs you focus new zealand's
她有多次被带到飞船上的意识清醒的经历
and has had many conscious experiences she's being taken to both croft many many times
她在飞船上还被展示看到了她的孩子
she's also been shown her children on the croft
她会出现在你们面前
and she's got to confranse some of you that's
也许许多疾病依然如机器人般无法治疗
perhaps still failed that a lot of diseases in grades are in fact robotic like
因为那是她的经验
creatures because that's not being her experience
而这不是我的许多客户的经验
and it's not being the experience of many of my clients
我没有进入他人的研究中 我没有意图进入他们的研究中
now i can go on other people's research i have no intention of going into that
因为我实际上不知道他们是怎么工作的 他们的客户是什么样
their research because i don't actually know 4how they've worked all their clients
或者是那样的事情 我只知道的是我的客户告诉我的事情
or anything like that i only know what my clients are telling me
因此从此刻起 我会说他们对于这些事情的理解
psalm ninety going for this moment in terms of the understanding they've given me of what they understand about these things
苏珊告诉我的一件事情是
one of the things that suzanne has told me
当她在飞船上时
is that when she's on the onboard croft
她同某些特殊的外星人有联系 她非常了解他们
she has particular connection to some features she knows them well
她说她的外星朋友很有幽默感
and she says and they have a sense of humor
她说除此之外 她还发现那些外星人极其的有爱心 极其的有同情心 极其的友善
and she said apart from that you know they are she has found them to be extremely lobbying extremely compassionate an extremely kind of one
她曾告诉我的一件事是
of the incidents in regression its laws that she told me
当她在飞船上学习时
when she was learning things on the call to use her mind
其中一个外星人会陪着她
was when one of the beings was accompanying her down
当她返回家中后 那个外星人会在她的脑海里给她展现 他正用以太形式的胳膊环绕着她
and she said the being in his mind showtime that he was sending an eckford on around to tell evan of
用这种方式告诉她：他在陪伴着她 照顾着她
that he was with marilyn was looking off to her
那就是那个外星生命以他的方式告诉苏珊 他在照顾着她
and it was his way of showing that he had he was carrying for her and she
苏珊也觉察到了这点 并且在头脑中用她的以太胳膊环抱了她的外星朋友
could see this and to show off to show what he had left she sent in africa alm
她承认：她完全懂了他的意思
and he acknowledge the fact that she denied well
这些是非常有趣的细节
and these are really interesting little details
她甚至从这些经历中被教导了
she even talked from this experience that when she was being told
她将会遇见某个特别的人物 她描述道在摇篮后面的小生命
she was going to meet someone special she describes skipping along the corridor in behind the little being
以及那个小生命是如何发笑的
and how they're being was highly amused
因为你看不到脸上的动作 你不必那么做 因为一切都是心灵感应完成的
so because you don't see the face move you don't need to because everything is in the mind in the
这是非常令人着迷的经历
this is a bit tically fascinating and experience
苏珊被告知  要她特意从新西兰飞来见我
that sushan had she was told to come and see me unhappy regression she fluid from new zealand right
她被告知这是一场特殊的经历 一定要对我们探索的保持开放的态度
but she was told that this was one she shouldn't have any uh... coming with any mandate any particular experience you have to be open to what we explored
这完全是一场非意识的经历
so this was totally in any way uh... not a conscious uh... experience
但我相信这些事情有着深刻的意义
but i want to demonstrate something very i'm very very profound
我叫苏珊 汉森
lucy's and he says
我来自新西兰的一家UFO接触研究机构
greater in new zealand UFO setting in contact  research network called UFO i think you can take me seriously critical
从童年起我就有同外星种族接触的经历
i have experience contact with extra speci
今天我要讲诉的是两次在飞船上的经历
today i would like to  descripe two directly related experience on board craft
可以证明有些灵魂被带到外星人那里接受教育 并且是为了人类未来利益正在进行的有建设性意义的项目的一部分
which  some souls are altered by ET spicies as a part of ongoing programes and agendas for the future benefit for mankind
1962年 当时我9岁
in nineteen sixty two nos in use some
我被带到一艘宇宙飞船上 在那间房间里 还有其他一些人类孩子
i was taken onboard the craft and until lunch from a year and than i had visited often without the human children
在那里我们被安排同外星人的孩子在一起 与他们进行频率的接触和交往
he will end to end region socialized comfortably in constantly without the species of ET children
我们用手和心灵感应在一起交流
using constantly fee ncnd unity
偶尔我会被一个灰人外星人带出去 见见在飞船上的其他孩子
on this information on strike and signed by me no granny when asked if i'd like to mention of the child summer onboard the craft
在我继续播放苏珊的录音之前 请你们注意一下这幅图画中那个小摇篮
before i go any further i think that i just want you to be aware of the little cradle
当苏珊第一次看到那个摇篮时 她就泪流满面了
and that the ticket cradle women sit down for sort you best into tears
她说她知道那个摇篮
and she's as i know that credo
事实上她的童年非常的艰难
and she described the fact that when she had and she had a very difficult childhood
那时 她和她的地球家人有一段创伤的时期
that when she'd had a particular traumatic time on uh... with hank human family
她经常被放进那个摇篮里
she was put on that creko
那个摇篮有某种特别的频率可以重新平衡她的能量
and he's actually had certain frequencies that would reap rebalance your energy field
她已经泪流满面了 因为她被给予了如此美好的怜悯和爱
and she passed into tears because she acts being shown such compassion and such love
那个灰人通过心灵感应的方式 给我讲述了一些与儿童生活有关的图片、思想和解释
the great eloquent technique and then through its pictures and explanations made regarding the strolled in its long
但是他给出的信息量实在过于庞大,我在有意识状态很难回忆起来
but the bond and financial stupid to return consciously
我只好.......
analysis linked with an eye on creation regarding meeting a nutrient
灰人告诉我这些孩子们还会留在这里
the guy tell me about the child with considerable kenya n_r_c_'s there's
好像他还有一些事情没有告诉我
something he was not you telling me
但是他在那次会议中需要我的合作
but he was thinking my cooperation with this nation
我们被带到了一个小房间中等候
we proceeded to a small room and wanted
在那里我很高兴见到了一些新朋友
and i felt excited about meeting new friends
两个灰人走进了房间 他们中间还漂浮着一个蓝色的光球
to rising to the room with a vibrant they will be like those in need between
我非常吃惊 因为我原本以为进来的会是新来的孩子
is less deductible on surprise had been expected to trial to arrive
我感受到了深刻的爱的感觉
uh... experience profound feelings of love and familiarity and somebody's unexpected thoughts
灰人告诉我 未来我会爱上这个蓝色的光球
the great only already love the sport of lines in the future
因为他会是我的儿子
as it would become my son
这里有个复杂的灵魂系统
here if they do it as both the souls into complex system
而且告诉我在我出生之前我就明白这套系统了
and said i had known it since before my underneath
灰人直接在我的头脑里下载了三条信息
the gray began in nineteen th monge mind download consisting of three strains of information
第一条就让我很困惑
the first just come to my my shins and confusion
灰人想让我和光球了解彼此 未来的母亲和孩子
they want us to get to know each other featured mother and son
而且还会观察我们是怎么互相连结这种关系的
and i wouldn't say if you are related to each other
很多信息直接进入到了我的潜意识 包括了这项工程的目的
essay constrained and they did extensive information into my subconscious conceding that this is the spreadsheet
新的基因创造了我孩子的身体 他将会在飞船上接受教育
the genetics involved in the creation of my son's body and agility detention he would receive onboard cropped
包括他的孩童时期和起源
buys is a child attending his sources lasalle st
他告诉我由于某些特定的原因
which he told me he had been enhanced unaltered by dean for specific papers
最后第三个灰人将我带回到了当下 一个九岁的孩子
finally has been strained brought my mind back to the present is a night your old child
还把我留下来同那个光球玩了一会儿
and i leave me declines the bull for a while
我试着和那个球连结上
i tried to relate to the bull unphased asking it to bounce
但是没有反应
by dysfunction at the unresponsive
我觉得有点失望就坐在了地板上
without disappointed and set them on the flu
忽然我感到那个光球在注视着我 而且在想些什么
suddenly i felt as if i was being watched and becoming the way the bulls thinking at me
然后它落到了我的肩膀上 同我一起快乐的交流玩耍
it does seem to down onto my shoulder and winston racing around the room communicating happily
不一会儿 灰人又回来了
dot i want to send to grace retained
他们对这次见面很满意
banks pay satisfaction amazing he's gone well
他们把光球带走了 而我感到很悲伤和孤独
truman's approval of lies away and also dates in unison long
灰人向我保证我还会见到光球很多次 直到我的儿子出生
graduate me that we would need taking many times up until the died at the summer people when
然后我们回到了其他孩子当中
so we came to me the other children they're interacting
1983年 我二十八岁 第一次怀孕
in nineteen ninety three now i a strange in eight years old you need to fill two in my face pregnancy
我被带到了飞船上
i was taken on board craft
我记得是当时有两个外星人协助我躺在了一张摇篮床上
my memory begins with may being assisted down a corridor by two to arrange taste a mixture of species
他们很关心我 因为我怀孕了
nice christensen from the inside being held throughout the pregnancy
他们轻柔的将我带到了一个小房间中
insanity nearly supposedly is needed a small room
他们把我扶到了一个类似沙发的座位上
to help me onto a shelf life bead and we're joined by right
然后对我解释说他们会将某个人“溶入”到我的身体当中
he explained that they are bringing someone to meet with me
我有点担心一切会不会好起来
and i was not speak unseen to see the thing would be fun
他将手放在了我的额头上
holding his hand on my phone
告诉我他首先会激活我潜意识中的一些记忆
he told me he faced needed to retrace the name respond months subconscious
那些童年时代就植入的部分
which had been invaded the in childhood
我的脑海中立即浮现出了大量的画面 过去我同那个蓝色的光球种种的联系 情感上的记忆
immediately my mind was filled with images emotions and memeries of past meetings  meetings associated with the bulls blunt
我真的是满脸泪水了 因为我意识到我灵魂上的孩子就要出生了
and i'm trying really to you fellas i realized it was the solve much are seen to be born
正当我十分激动的时候 一群灰人孩子来到了我的房间
as he calmed formations a group of eighty children coming into the room
带着和蓝色光球类似的能量
bringing with them the now familiar soul opal having tea
灰人说他会同这个刚出生的孩子待在飞船上 直到他长大
he starts and these young ladies had grown up onboard the craft with the song
他们会照顾他 支持他
and i would play an integral part in supporting him in his life
融合的过程真的是很兴奋
there was a really of excitement is the process of making began
灰人调整了我的身体的能量适应了那个光球灵魂的能量
the grand slam on the campus in right down to two p m on bloody thing teens energy of the cell
以便我的身体不至于受到太大刺激
necessary to complete shock to my body
在这个过程中 我的声音变得越加的迟缓 几乎无法分辨
during that knows it would be issue with me really good point becomes really slow and almost indistinguishable at this point
我的身体感到很冷 而且麻木
and my body felt cold and mom
慢慢的那个灵魂进入到了我的身体 成为了我的孩子
suddenly the selling tonight buddy and the body of my child to be
我感到身体出于失重状态 之后灰人又将我恢复了正常
i felt confused with delight in weightlessness is the chrysler lee brought them on the table doesn't break to normal looking
灰人声称我的儿子很快就会出生了
he started my son would be polite which he was
他会陪同我的儿子长大
and that he would be company through his life by what shes
会为他提供一些必要的系统
but in a moment eat to describe pretty consistent and provide for them
灰人又补充到还有数以千计的孩子出生在和他一样的世界里
he and there are thousands of children being born a boy
他们都参与了一项积极改变的工程当中 加速了人类种族的进化
leblanc and house in an extensive project create positive challenges nixon arises either location from within the human species
这两次经历描述了灵魂状态的复杂性
he says the reason is the list right soul statement
而且揭示了外星人灵魂为了某些特别的目的转世到了地球上
in relation to a scale involve themselves in the housing on the street the specific basis
这挑战了我们要重新评估我们目前对灵魂有限的理解
it chlange us the real issues at hand understanding of the song
灵魂在我们出生之前就已存在
the cells existence before implantation
灵魂的进化不单单是通过重复生生世世的轮回
and the idea and so you know it's not just a repeated cycles of lifetimes
而且还可以通过外星力量的介入而得到加强 改变和教育 我再为你们重复一遍
based on experience is but could also be enhanced alternate any education by external forces does speak for space is not just saying that he can foreign
“这两次经历说明了灵魂状态的复杂性
these two experiences illustrate the complexity of the soul state
而且揭示了外星人灵魂为了某些特别的目的转世到了地球上
and reveal extraterrestrial involvement with souls incarnating for specific purposes
这挑战了我们要重新评估我们目前对灵魂有限的理解
it challenges us to reassess our current limited understanding of the soul
灵魂在转世之前就已存在
the souls existence before incarnation
灵魂的进化不单单是通过重复生生世世的轮回
and the idea for the sole involves not just to repeat it cycles or lifetimes of personal experiences
而且还可以通过外星力量的介入而得到加强 改变和教育”
but can also be in hobbs altered and educated by external forces or species
这对于你们当中的有些人来说可能是非常难以理解的观念
and this is going to for some of you i think the quite difficult concepts
我理解那一点
and i understand that
而似乎对于我来说
but what it seems to be and suggesting to me
很显然的丹娜昨天谈到的
and obviously and wichita and talked about yesterday
我们也许不止是只看了事实 我们看到了外星人
that we are not just perhaps looking at the fact that we are and looking extraterrestrials
不同纬度间 也许甚至是我们的未来
into dimensional strength and end holes and a half even some from our own future
而底线似乎是如这位十五岁的孩子看到的
but the boston line seems to be as this fifteen-year-old that was seeing
TED叔叔和爷爷作为光球也是整个全景图的一部分
uncalled ted and granddad assaults of lights that they are also part of this big picture on these beings
他们都是与我们互动的对象或是造访者 然而这一切似乎比我们曾经想到的都要深远的多
that we are interacting with or having encounters with and this seems to be far more going on than we ever thought
在那种意义上说并没有分离
and there is that that sense that there is no actual separation in that sense
我认为现在我要说的一件事情是
i think that one thing i want to say now
所谓的“外星人绑架”事件 我部分参与了由Simon Hobby Wilson2000年在西澳大利亚撰写的论文《萨满主义与绑架之比较》
is that the abductions a so-called abduction scenario by participated in a thesis bite simon hobby wilson that laws of the comparisons between shamanism and adoptions in western australia in two thousand
Simon发现的是
and what simon discovered
两者之间非常相似 比如术语上说的转化 疗愈等等
the parallels will quite fascinating in terms of transformation healing except for except rap
而我的感觉是我们所看到的正是现代萨满体验
and my sense is that what we're saying is a modern-day sha manic experience
我们的挑战是转化恐惧 准备好接受我们多维度的本质
where we are being challenge to try and send off fears to be prepared for our multi-dimensional nature
而这都是那个挑战的一部分
and this is all part of dot challenge
我们是否会超越我们限制性的恐惧 接受并准备好进入更高的纬度
are we going to go beyond our limited fears to actually accept and be prepared for working in and uh... through not only and dimensions but beyond that
这就是我们的新身体 也许是新的硬件驱动
and this is what on new body perhaps is spent on new hard drive
我们的下载都是为了这个做的准备   因此这实际上真的在许多许多的层面对我们提出了挑战
i'm not downloading is preparing us full so it's actually challenging us for many many levels
而有些人不需要那样的经历
in and some obviously don't need that kind of experience
因为我目前看到了一大批的类似的经历
because i'm seeing a broad range now of experiences from their sat twenty to thirty percent off
大致有20%-30%的绑架 或是所谓的绑架经历  在某种意义上我会说是“所谓的”绑架
the adoption also quoted duction experience in the sense that i will say so-called because for many of my clients
因为我的很多客户  当我把他们带入到催眠状态时 我问过他们的潜意识
when i've taken to mean to hypnosis and i have lost their subconscious
他们是否在任意层面上 非自愿参与这一人类经历 他们当中没有一个人说"不"
Have they on any level any level consented to this part of a human experience and not one of them yet has said to me
他们中大部分人都对我说 这是在他们出生之前同意的
most of them will tell me it was before they came here
他们中有些人说 在那个空间询问他们自己那个问题时 他们会将他们自己表述成光球
and some of the night actually said and off that question in that space themselves and then describe themselves as a bull of light
他们中还有人说在他们来地球之前 他们是外星人
who uh... and some of them have also said that they went on human before they ame here they were extra-terrestrial
他们承担起了协助这个星球进化的使命
and they have undertaken to come to this planet to assist this plant to evolve
现在不是由我来对那些经历的理解做出评判
now it's not for me to judge that understanding all that experience
我问对他们说 "这些对你来说有意义吗 你会对此有共鸣吗？"
if this is what that individual and i will say to them does this make sense to you does it resonates
而每一次他们都会说 YES
and everytime they will say yes
有一件事非常有趣 有一位年轻的女士 她有着这样的意识
but one of the things that was quite fascinating one of the young ladies who was aware that your consciousness
她对我说：是的 我就是这样  她谈到她的外星人部分的自己对此事感觉很酷 但是她的人类部分的自己却没有意识到这是如此的艰难
she said to me yes i did but price it she said the extraterrestrial caught me was cool with it but she said the human part of me idn't realize it was going to be so hard
这就是她的评论
which is that comment
但我要说的是这只是他们潜意识中的理解 而不是我个人的评价
but what i'm saying is this is an only from net understanding with their subconscious it's not the named to judge or assimilate all
或者是将任何我个人的想法或感情参杂其中 我要努力做到的是将他们个人的理解对他们来讲是说的通的
even uh... trying and in any way uh... for any of mine unforeseen feelings with this what i'm trying to do with my work is to keep her person the understanding that make sense to then intensive
在他们自己的现实经历当中   而底线是我发现无论是有多么的怪异
understanding their own experience in reality and that the at the bottom line is that what i find is no matter how strangely it may be
甚至是展示出了他们的父母亲并非人类
even to being shown and one of their parents not being human
这对于大多数人来说都是难以面对的 其中有一个案例实际上发生在一个警察身上 顺便提一下 他是Gary
which is pretty confronting for most people and when one of those was actually a policeman by the way gary
非常具有挑战性
uh... it was quite challenging
令我感兴趣的是 不会在意识清醒时说出或是承认
farrakhan what's interesting to me is that this is not something that would consciously wanna say or even admit to
但是他们对我说在很深的层次上他们会对此很共鸣 这对我来说就很重要了
but they say to me on a deeper level it actually resonates and that's all that matters to me is
因为对他们来说是有意义的 而使得他们能够整合这一经历 疗愈他们自己 并且在这条道路上继续前行
that it makes sense to them what is the last thing to do if integrate this experience and heal nd move on and expanding their own way
无论是什么对他们有意义就够了 而不是要把这一经历限制在冲突的第三纬度的小盒子里
in whatever makes sense to them so instead of actually being in conflict with that dimensional paradigm in trying to fit this experience into that box
他们要接受他们在两个层面上的人类体验
except that they're operating on two levels of human experience
一旦他们接受这个事情 对两个层面来说都没有问题
and once they can accept in both  being that is OK
他们就可以通过那样的方式成长 整合 及疗愈
they can actually playwith that integrate heal
过上正常的生活 他们正常的状态对于这个世界是非常难以承认的 因为这个世界是否认那个（外星）现实世界的
and live normal lives and normalize state which is the very difficult in the world that denies that very reality
因此我希望我能给你们一些值得思考的东西
so with that i hope i've given you something to think about i'd also hope
我也希望你们理解 我并不期望你会对我给你们展示的东西能照单全收
that you understand i'm not expecting you to take on board everything that i've shown you
我所做的就是给你们提供了我从1600位客户的案例中学习和理解到的东西
well i would like to do is all for you what i'm learning and uh... understanding from my sixteen hundred cases
这就是目前为止我以我自己的方式将这一切整理在了一起 试着让这些都有意义
so far and this is what's uh... i've put together as a way of myself trying to make sense of it
我不知道我在这里到了什么程度
i have no idea if how far on write-up uh... and with this or not
但是只要任何事情对你们有意义的话 即使只是引起了你们的好奇心
but have anything makes sense to your thick even just insights your curiosity
那基本上也是我有必要做的事情
then that bs basically or i need to do
我想感谢你们所有的到场听众  我还有机会回答几个问题
and i want to thank you all for being a wonderful audience tonight have coded chance for a few
如果你们有什么提问的  我会很高兴回答
questions so if you've got any questions i'm quite happy talker
非常有趣的问题 实际上他们从没有对我说过
it's a very interesting question they've never actually talk to me
他们在哪里下载的这些外星语言
about and where they eat and downloaded the sandwiches
他们中有些人说这是一种“下载”
and some of them say it is a download and on what happy at that
有趣的是我遇到过一位年轻的先生
interestingly i met at a young attention
他是英国人 他来澳大利亚的珀斯找到我
hit with english who came to pass
他对我谈及到了他的经历 而他对我说的是 在心灵感应这个部分
he came to me about his experiences and what he did say to me intensive the telepathic part of that
有一次他在野外露营时弄丢了帐篷 一件崭新的帐篷
once that and he'd actually lost his scout camp which is hispanic apne go into the scouts
他回家之后就没有再见过那个帐篷了 是一次奇怪的经历
and when he came home he didn't have it and it had a strange experience
当我们谈起他的这个经历时 他说道了一件有趣的事情
and when we explored his experience one of the interesting things he said to me
当他在飞船上的时候 他所听到的一切都是一团混乱
was when he was up on the croc everything he was carrying around in his mind was a jumble
他说就像是我要把我的心思调整到某个频率上
he said but it was like i have to cheer
就像是你要收听无线电广播
mine mine too if we could see other just like you were directly a signal andy
他说我之后就可以非常清楚的听到一切了
said knock it here everything very very clearly
他说非常有趣 因为他是第一次听到那些
he said which is quite fascinating is the first time i've heard that
而我理解的是他们在飞船上是一切都是心灵感应的
now and from what i can gather it's all telepathic on the croft
而这似乎是某种下载
uh... but be seen to be downloading zen
也符合米歇尔描述的灵魂的语言 宇宙的语言
the way we shall describes missile languages all universal languages
所以如果我们能接受这点 我能理解对你们某些人来说这是一个巨大的提升
so if we take on board and that's a big lake this summer if you like to understand
也许这些人中现在是以人类形式生活的 实际上是来自其他的星系的生命
that perhaps some of these individuals that now in human form actually came from other stall system so whatever
而他们感觉到的是他们的家人在那里
and they feel like they're family is out there
那就是他们对我说的
and that's what they will tell me
你可能会奇怪这些是不是他们亲口说的
uh... you have to wonder whether or not this is the from that origins and i mean
而我的意思是这都是真真切切的事实 因为在情感方面来说
this is really tangible stuff for them because the emotional
这是非常意义深远的 他们中很多人都说 “我不想待在这里 我不喜欢这个地方 这里不像是家园”
cited a sweet very profound and many things that i don't want to be here i don't like this place
我想举一个例子 一个五岁的孩子曾说
and to give an example of what a five-year-old actually said
她对她的父母说过
about her understanding she said to her parents aces
这对父母来说实在是难以面对
terribly confronting to parents
当时她五岁 她对她的妈妈说
and she was five when she said this to another
她说“你们不是我真正的父母 我的父母在太空里”
she said your not my real parents my parents are in space
还好她母亲意识到了她的特殊经历
and another frightfully had been aware of her own experiences and
而且能够照顾到她女儿
so was able to sort of on a what she'd had order was saying so and order
她对她的女儿说 如果是那样的话 “实际上我看上去不是这个（人类）样子的”
she said her daughter well if you're not if that's so and she said i don't really
她五岁的女儿说
look like this the five year old daughter said in adored and another said
妈妈说 “那么你看上去是什么样子的 你可以画下来吗”
what what do you look like that you could utorrent and she said no
女儿说 “不 因为会吓到你的”
because you'd be frightened
我们谈的是一个五岁的女孩
now we're talking about a five year old girl
我听过太多的人都说过,
i've heard of so many times from different people saying
“我觉得好像我是被收养的 我的家人似乎不是我真正的家人 即使我很爱我的家人和父母 我感觉我还是不属于这里
i feel like i've been adopted my family doesn't feel like my real family and even though i love my family in my parents i still i don't belong
我感觉我属于那里（太空）” 房间里一定有人和这件事有关系
i feel i belong out there there are big people in this room that relate to that absolutely
他们疯了吗
now all the crazy
数千的人都疯了吗？他们会有那样的感觉？还是说事实上他们正告诉我们一些需要我们注意到的事情
off thousands of people crazy that the feeling like that or is it in fact telling us something that we need to be aware of
你知道的 那就是我要给你们提供的一切
you know and and that's all i'm i'm putting to use on her as a second give you any more than that
谢谢 确实是存在着许多不同的观点
you know in this isn't this a lot of and different different opinions about you know
关于它们为什么要这样做 有什么议程有很多意见
我认为我是个十分有逻辑理智的人
i think i'm a pretty logical kind of a percent
我是这样的方式看待这个的
and the way that i look at it is this
如果他们把我们带到飞船上 教导我们宇宙学 许多不同的事情 还有人类的起源
if they're not taking asks onto these crompton teaching us cosmology and all the different things about the origin of the species teaches
怎么样使用我们的心智 教导我们怎么进行治疗等等这类事情
how to use our minds teaching us how to heal annoyance thing
为什么他们会烦恼 如果他们要占领我们的话 为什么他们不把我们单独放在这里
why would they thought that if they can take us at port just why don't they just need a saloon and let's
因为我们自己在某个方面来说已经做了很好的工作
face it we're doing a pretty good job of taking ourselves apart anyway
所以对我来说似乎很不合逻辑
so for me it doesn't seem very logical
而这是我遗漏了些什么
and this is something i'm missing here
去操心 去帮助新人类（如果你喜欢这种说法的话）的成长 探索和改变成为多维度的生命
to bother too help that note uh... new human if you like to grow and expand in change become multi-dimensional
除非这里还有其他事情正在进行着 我实在是看不出他们最终会接管人类
unless there is something else going on here and i certainly can't see it would be ultimately to take over the species
我确实相信他们有许多计划
i do believe that they have
有些计划是跟我们有关 但是有些却是为了理解他们自身
uh... a lot of programs and some of those ought to do with offs but some of those it to do with understanding themselves
我可以给你们部分的答案
and i will just give you as as part of that offset
一位绅士最近找到我做催眠回溯 他被带到飞船上
and i can't win that just recently i did a regression whitney was taken up onto a croft
他告诉我那艘宇宙飞船三十二英里长
and he told me that the cost is thirty two miles long
然后他对我说他看到了某种类似水族馆一样的东西
and then he said he saw thoughtfulness in a kind of aquarium
他问那个外星人说 这是什么
and he said to the games what is this
外星人们给他展示了某种科技 很显然是在其他宇宙中创造出了某种类型的黑洞
and they showed him some technology which apparently creates a kind of worm hall into how the universe is
他们说“我们对你们所做的事情 也是我们在其他宇宙中做的事情
and they said what we're doing with you is what we're doing enough the universe
我们在其他宇宙中播种 我们在造物 有朝一日你们也会这么做的”
is we seat of the universe is and we create just as you will too
你们可以接受 也可以不接受
now you can take that only two as you will
但我认为
but it seems to me
既然他们不嫌麻烦的来帮助我们
that if they thought the to change in all trucking attics and gradually and hearts
逐步的以他们的方式提高我们的能力 以便我们能够成为多维度的生命
our abilities in the way that they're doing so that we can become multi-dimensional
他们这样做是为了什么呢
why would they bought them
如果议程不是这样的话 似乎对我来说我们正在被帮助着改变和成长
if it wasn't uh... agenda which seems to me to suggest we're being helped to changing to grow
直到我们理解了我们可以成为多维度属性的生命
until understand on multi-dimensional nd the magnificent nature of what we could be
我相信我们所有人都有那样的潜力
cuz i believe we all have the potential for that
也许只是也许 他们向我们伸出了援助之手
and perhaps just perhaps they giving us a helping hand and i believe
我相信迄今为止我所看到的正是如此...
from what i've seen so far anyway that's the case
女士们 先生们 非常感谢
演讲者MARY RODWELL女士的更多信息请浏览：http://www.acern.com.au/
相关主题的书《来自宇宙的新小孩(世界超能儿童科学调查档案)》